Guide to the William T. Cannady Architectural Projects Records, 1956-2018 MS 577
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Sketches, awards, files, and other papers, 147486
  - Award - The Southern Home Award - Schulte Residence, 1990; 147498 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - On the Boards - Tatlici Villa, March 26, 1990; 147497 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Architecture Honor Award - Northern Trust Bank, April 8, 1995; 147496 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - Renovation/Restoration - David Taylor Classics Car Museum, Galveston TX, April 13, 1996; 147495 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Award - AIA Houston Chapter - 25 Year Award - The Brochstein House, April 16, 1999; 147494 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Award - Progressive Architecture 25th Anniversary Awards Program - Citation - Lovett Square, undated; 147493 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Award - First Awards - Merit Award for Innovative Remodeling of a Commercial Structure, undated; 147492 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Award - First Awards - Merit Award for Innovative Remodeling of a Residential Structure, undated; 147491 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Award - Texas Architecture for Health Design Awards (TAH-DA!) - Silver Award, Interiors - Sid W. Richardson Institute for Preventative Medicine, undated; 147490 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Nomination for fellow in the AIA, December 1977; 148462 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Harrell and Hamilton, Inc. - Report of Examination, March 31, 1970; 148463 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Rick Gardner Photography, Houston, TX, c. 1975; 147993 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - American Academy in Rome, 1967-1968; 148464 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1976, 1996; 148465 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - Texas Architect and related material, April 1979; 148466 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Calendars, 1967-1968; 148467 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Pinboard item - The American Society of Planning Officials certificate of membership, c. 1967; 148468 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Pinboard item - City of Houston proclamation: Model Cities Application Workers, April 23, 1968; 148469 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Pinboard items - Drawings, photographs, postcards, and membership cards, 148470 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Pinboard items - Clippings, advertisements, brochures, and other papers, 148471 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Invitation and photos - party celebrating ten years of practice in architecture, Wm. T. Cannady and Anderson Todd, c. 1972; 148472 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Invitation - surprise birthday party, Herb Paseur's 50th, November 6, 1975; 148473 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Invitation to cocktail party, December 11, 1987; 148474 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - European trip (folder 1/2), 1969; 148475 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - European trip (folder 2/2), 1969; 148476 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cartoon - O. Jack Mitchell, Earle Britton, and William T. Cannady, undated; 148477 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Presentation - Why Houston Why? (Paris), July 7, 1984; 148478 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Program - Irish Cultural Festival, with Cannady contribution, c. 1987; 148479 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Program - Harvard Comes to Houston, Peter G. Rowe introduced by Wm. T. Cannady, March 3, 1988; 148480 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Brochure - NOAH: Neighborhood Organization for Acceptable Housing, c. 1997; 148481 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Booklet - 45 Years...William T. Cannady, FAIA, Architect, Rice School of Architecture, February 7-28, 2003; 148482 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Exhibit at Rice - framed projects, 2003; 148483 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Mayor's Advisory Committee on Housing - Houston (folder 1/2), 1967-1968; 148983 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mayor's Advisory Committee on Housing - Houston (folder 2/2), 1967-1968; 148984 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce - Advance Urban Analysis Committee, 1968; 148985 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce - Advance Urban Analysis Committee, May 1968-March 1969; 148986 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Citizens' Advisory Committee on Housing - Houston, 1968-1969; 148987 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - City of Houston Committees - AIA, AUA, CACH, 1968-1969; 148988 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce - Future Studies Committee, 1970-1971; 148989 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Series III: Articles and books, 148455
  - Architecture at Rice, "#14," Urban Design by Third Year Undergraduates, August 1964; 148068 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Architecture at Rice, "#16", August 1965; 148067 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Planning Study for Air Cargo Development at LAX, c. 1960, 148062 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - New Schools for New Towns, Educational Facilities Laboratories and Rice U., 1966, 148059 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Texas Magazine, article on pg. 21, 20 Aug. 1967, 148057 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Progressive Architecture, April 1968, 148052 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Progressive Architecture, Dec. 1968; Cannady (St. Barnabas) on pgs. 102-105, 148050 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Misc. lecture materials and calendars, 1970s, 148045 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Architectural Design, Jan. 1970; with Cannady article on IAH, 148044 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Beating the Systems Game," in Progressive Architecture, March 1970, 148043 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Selecting Building Materials," in Progressive Architecture, March 1970, 148042 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Public Management, articles on Urban Design, vol. 52, no. 6, June 1970, 148040 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - The Texas Architect, with article on St. Barnabas Episcopal Church, Jan. 1971, 148034 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Architectural Design, Volume XLI, April 1971, with article on 'TET Center Houston", 148033 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Faith & Form, with reference to St. Barnabas Episcopal Church, Fall 1971, 148030 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rice University Faculty Club Forum, 1972-1973; Cannady on pgs. 26-27, 148024 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Architectural Design, Volume XLIII, Jan. 1972, with article on One Shell Plaza, 148022 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Architectural Design, Volume XLIII, Feb. 1972, 148021 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "Architecture Shapes Man?" 34th Annual Meeting of the Texas Society of Architects, 1973, 148018 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "Award Winning Architecture USA" First Edition, 1973, 148017 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Architectural Record of Houses, Mid-May 1973, 148013 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Architectural Design, vol. XLIII, Nov. 1973, with article on Houston Galleria, 148011 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Greater Houston Living, Real Estate Guide, Nov./Dec. 1973, 148010 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design News, Dec. 1973, 148009 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Texas Architect, no. 1 vol. 24, March/April 1974, 148000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Texas Architect, no. 2 vol. 24, May/June 1974; with article on Cannady House, 147999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Architectural Design, vol. XLIV, June 1974; with article on DFW Airport, 147997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Texas Architect, no. 5 vol. 24, Nov./Dec. 1974, 147995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 25, July/Aug. 1975; with article on Crane House, 148990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - A Monthly Journal of World Architecture and Urbanism, no. 50, c. 1975, with article on Cannady House, 147992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Houston Home & Garden, Aug. 1975; with article on Cannady House, 147989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Texas Architect, no. 6 vol. 25, Nov./Dec. 1975; with photograph and award for Brochstein Residence, 147988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Texas Architect, no. 3 vol. 26, May/June 1976; with Cannady interview in "Creativity" article, 147984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 26, July/Aug. 1976, 147983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Texas Architect, no. 5 vol. 26, Sept./Oct. 1976; with article on Brochstein Residence, 147982 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Texas Architect, no. 6 vol. 26, Nov./Dec. 1976; with awards of merit for University of Petroleum and Minerals, Dahran, Saudi Arabia and Children's Mental Health Services of Houston, 147981 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - A View of Contemporary World Architects, published in Japan, 1977; Cannady on pg. 197, 147979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Texas Society of Architects Newsletter, 1977, 147977 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Intercourse 7, published by the Rice School of Architecture, 22 Feb. 1977, 147974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Texas Architect, no. 2 vol. 27, March/April 1977, with article on Children's Mental Health Services of Houston, 147973 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - The Tulanian, Summer 1977, with article on Rice-Tulane competition to design National Oil & Gas Museum, 147972 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Inland Architect, July 1977, with article on Houston, TX, 147971 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Progressive Architecture, July 1977; with reference to Duchesne Gymnasium, 147970 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Newsletter 10, American Institute of Architects, Oct. 1977, 147969 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Royal Institute of British Architects--Journal, Dec. 1977, with article on Houston, TX architecture and Cannady quote, 147968 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Progressive Architecture, Dec. 1977, Cannady news on pg. 20, 147967 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Texas Architect, no. 6 vol. 27, Nov./Dec. 1977; award of merit for Walker's Mark Townhouses, 147966 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - American General Insurance Company, Annual Report, 1978, 147963 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Texas Society of Architects Newsletter, No. 1, 1978, 148992 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Progressive Architecture, Jan. 1978; Cannady on pg. 79, 147959 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - On Campus, Rice Newsletter, 20 Jan. 1978, Cannady on pg 5, 148993 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - News, Harvard Graduate School of Design, March 1978; Cannady on pg. 10, 147957 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Houston Home & Garden, March 1978; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pg. 230, 147956 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Texas Architect, no. 2 vol. 28, March/April 1978; with article on Walker's Mark Townhouses, 147955 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Sallyport, April 1978; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pg. 16, 147954 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Texas Architect, no. 3 vol. 28, May/June 1978, 147953 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Housing, June 1978, Cannady on pg. 36, 147952 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 28, July/Aug. 1978, 147951 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Architecture at Rice Newsletter, vol. 1 no. 1, Fall 1978, 147950 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - The Architectural Review, Nov. 1978, Cannady on pgs. 280, 296, 147949 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Investiture of AIA Fellows, 1979, 147948 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Houston Engineer, Feb. 1979, with article on IAH, 147943 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Houston Home & Garden, Feb. 1979, with two pages on Walker's Mark Townhouses, 147942 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Texas Architect, no. 2 vol. 29, March/April 1979; Houston Residential Design Awards--Walker's Mark, 147941 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Texas Society of Architects Newsletter, 27 March 1979, Cannady on pg. 3, 147940 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Texas Architect, No. 3 vol. 29, May/June 1979, 147938 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design, News, Summer 1979, 147937 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture, Inc., News, Summer 1979, 147936 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Amacadmy, The Newsletter of the American Academy in Rome, July 1979, 147935 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Progressive Architecture, Oct. 1979, Cannady (Lovett Square) on pgs. 64-67, 147934 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Texas Architect, no. 6 vol. 29, Nov./Dec. 1979, 147933 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Homes for Better Living Awards Program--Sunset Terrace submission, 1980, 147931 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Houston Home & Garden, April 1980; Cannady (Sunset Terrace) on pgs. 50-57, 147928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Toshi-Jutaku, April 1980; article on Lovett Square Apts., 147927 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fidelity's Interest, Summer 1980; "William Cannady Takes after Workaholic Father", 147926 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 30, July/Aug. 1980, 147924 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, Texas Society of Architects, 27 Aug. 1980; design award for Eastwood Park, 147923 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Texas Architect, no. 6 vol. 30, Nov./Dec. 1980, 147922 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Texas Society of Architects, 5 Dec. 1980, 147921 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - More Houses - Architects Design for Themselves, 1981; Cannady House on pg. 44-45, 147920 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Texas Medical Center, 1981 Annual Report, with mention of Sid W. Richardson Institute for Preventive Medicine, 147917 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter 3, American Institute of Architects, March 1981, with photograph and reference to Cannady Ranch, 147916 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Architectural Review, March 1981; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pgs. 134-135, 147915 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Texas Architect, no. 2 vol. 31, March/April 1981; Cannady (Eastwood Park) on pg. 43, 147914 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Houston Home & Garden, April 1981; Cannady (Round Top) on pgs. 82-83, 147913 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Texas Architect, no. 3 vol. 31, May/June 1981; Cannady (Round Top) on pg. 25, 147912 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Houston Home & Garden, July 1981; pg. 111, 147910 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Texas Homes, July/Aug. 1981; Cannady Ranch on pgs. 104-111, related correspondence and article on Rome, 147909 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 31, July/Aug. 1981; Friendswood on pgs. 52-53, 147908 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The Journal, a publication of the Methodist Hospital, Aug. 1981; Cannady (Chez Eddy) on pg. 10, 147907 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design News, Fall 1981; Cannady on pg. 14, 147906 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Houston, Dec. 1981; Cannady on pg. 35, 147905 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Housing, by John Macsai, 2nd edition, 1982; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pgs. 542-543, 147904 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Progressive Architecture, Feb. 1982, 147903 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Progressive Architecture, May 1982; Cannady on pg. 60, 147902 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Texas Architect, no. 3 vol. 32, May/June 1982, 147901 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - South Main Center Association, Newsletter, Summer 1982, 147900 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Texas Architect, no. 4 vol. 32, July/Aug. 1982, 147899 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Texas Homes, July 1982; Cannady on pg. 45, 147898 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Texas Homes, Aug. 1982, 147897 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Progressive Architecture, August 1982; Val Glitsch on pgs. 78-80, 147896 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Texas Society of Architects, Newsletter, 13 Aug. 1982, 147895 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Texas Architect, no. 5 vol. 32, Sept./Oct. 1982, 147894 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 32 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1982; Cannady (Cannady Ranch) on pg. 41, 147893 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Houston Home & Garden, Dec. 1982, 147892 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Newsletter 12, American Institute of Architects, Dec. 1982; Cannady (Sid Richardson Institute for Preventive Med.) on pg. 5, 147891 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - "A History of the Texas Society of Architects," by Hank Todd Smith, 1983; Cannady on pg. 117, 147890 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The American Institute of Architects--A history and directory of the College of Fellows, 1983, 147889 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Metro Stage One, Houston, TX, c. 1983, 147888 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - The Journal, Winter 1983, 147887 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 33 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1983; Cannady on pg. 27, 147886 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Harvard Graduate School of Design News, Jan./Feb. 1983, Cannady on pg. 10, 148998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Houston Magazine, March 1983; Cannady on pg. 70, 147884 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - GoodLife Houston, March 1983; Sid Richardson Institute for Preventive Medicine on pg. 52, 147883 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Cite, A Publication of the Rice Design Alliance, Spring 1983, pg. 12, 147882 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 33 no. 3, May/June 1983; Cannady (Reidel Lake House) on pg. 91, 148999 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Texas Society of Architects, Newsletter, 17 June 1983; Cannady on pg. 3, 147880 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 33 no. 4, July/Aug. 1983, Cannady on pg. 54, 147879 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Houston Business Journal, 4 July 1983; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 22, 147878 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Village News, Aug. 1983; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 1, 147877 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - South Main Center Association newsletter, Fall 1983; Cannady on pg. 7, 149000 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Houston Post, 8 Nov. 1983; news concerning Sid W. Richardson Institute, 147875 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 33 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1983, 147874 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Chocolatier, Newsletter of the Chocolate Bayou Theater Co., 1984; Cannady on pg. 2, 147873 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 34 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1984, 147872 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Sallyport, Feb./March 1984; Cannady on pg. 3, 147871 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 34 no. 2, March/April 1984; Cannady (Fayette County Savings and Loan) on pgs. 42-45, 147870 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - On Campus, 12 March 1984, 147869 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Faith & Form, Spring 1984; Cannady (Church of the Good Shepherd) on pg. 11, 147868 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Houston Home & Garden, April 1984; Cannady on pg. 116-117, 147867 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - The Village News, April 1984; Cannady on pg. 2, 147866 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - The Rice Thresher, 27 April 1984; Cannady on pgs. B4-B5, 147864 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 34 no. 3, May/June 1984; Cannady on pg. 34, 147863 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Home, July 1984; Cannady (Calfee House) on pgs. 46-47, 147862 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - The Village News, Sept. 1984; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 1, 147860 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 34 no. 5, Sept./Oct. 1984; Cannady on pg. 78, 147859 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Easy Living, Fall 1984; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pgs. 10-12, 147858 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Houston Home & Garden, Oct. 1984; Cannady on pg. 164, 147857 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Home, Nov. 1984; Cannady on pgs. 52-55, 147856 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Architecture Quarterly, November 1984; Cannady (Fayette Savings and Loan) on pgs. 80-81, 147855 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Architecture, Nov. 1984; Cannady (Fayette Savings and Loan) on pg. 81, 147854 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Houston Post--Design Today, 24 Nov. 1984; Cannady on pg. 1, 147853 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Houston Chronicle, Section 6, 29 Nov. 1984; Cannady and family on pg. 1, 147852 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Architects, Newsletter, 21 Dec. 1984; Cannady on pg. 5, 147851 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter, Texas Architects Committee, 1985; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 4, 147850 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - On Campus, Rice U., vol. 11 no. 12, 1985; Cannady on backpage, 147849 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Home, Jan. 1985; Cannady on pg. 81, 147845 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Architecture, Feb. 1985; Cannady (Fayette Savings and Loan) on pg. 6, 147843 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Houston on Stage, A Performing Arts Network Publication, March 1985; Cannady (Chocolate Bayou Theater) on multiple pages, 147842 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Cite, A publication of the Rice Design Alliance, Spring 1985; Cannady on pg. 15, 147841 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Village Life, April 1985; Cannady (Village Square Phase II) on pg. 2, 147840 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Houston Business Journal, 8 April 1985; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 19A, 147839 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Texas Homes, May 1985; Cannady on pg. 48, 147838 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Houston on Stage, A Performing Arts Network Publication, May 1985; Cannady (Chocolate Bayou Theater) on pg. 22, 147837 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 35 no. 3, May/June 1985; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 76, 147836 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter 6, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, June 1985; Cannady (Chocolate Bayou Theater) on pg. 9, 147835 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Houston Chapter of Commerce Magazine, July 1985; Cannady on pg. 26, 147834 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Village News, July/Aug. 1985; Cannady (Village Square) on pg. 2, 147833 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Report, Texas Society of Architects, Aug. 1985; Cannady on pg. 2, 147832 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Announcements, Rice U. School of Architecture, 1985-1986, 147831 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Newsletter 9, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Sept. 1985, 147830 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - College of Environmental Design News, UC Berkeley, Fall 1985; Cannady on pg. 25, 147829 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Houston Home & Garden, Oct. 1985; Cannady on pg. 34, 147828 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Houston City Magazine, 14 Oct. 1985; Cannady (Chocolate Bayou Theater) on pg. 14, 147827 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 35 no. 6, Nov./Dec. 1985; Cannady (Village Square) on pgs. 80-81, 147826 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Houston Business Journal, 18 Nov. 1985; Cannady (The Darlington) on pg. 22A, 147824 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Newsclipping, Houston Chronicle, 24 Nov. 1985; Cannady on pg. 23, 147823 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Houston Post, 30 Nov. 1985; Cannady on pg. 2G, 147822 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cite, A publication of the Rice Design Alliance, Winter 1985-1986; Cannady (Chocolate Bayou Theater) on pg. 8, 147820 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Architecture at the Crossroads, by Peter Adam, 1986, 147816 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Progressive Architecture, Jan. 1986; Cannady (Lovett Square) on pg. 142, 147811 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 36 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1986; Cannady (Sid Richardson Institute) on pg. 55, 147810 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Architectural Record, Feb. 1986; Cannady (Village Square and Church of the Good Shepherd) on pgs. 72-73, 147809 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - On Campus, Rice U., 10 Feb. 1986; Cannady on pg. 6, 147808 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Texas Business, March 1986; Cannady (Fayette Savings and Loan) on pg. 47, 147807 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Design Today, The Houston Post, 29 March 1986; Cannady (Church of the Good Shepherd) on pg. 1, 147806 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "Architectural Education: The Re-emergence of the Design Thesis," by Wm. T. Cannady, in Architectural Record, April 1986, pg. 43, 147805 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Sallyport, Publication of the Association of Rice Alumni, April/May 1986; Cannady on pg. 5, 147804 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Newsletter 5, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, May 1986; Cannady (Sid Richardson Institute) on pg. 3, 147803 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Architecture, May 1986; Cannady (Church of the Good Shepherd) on pg. 86, 147802 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - News, The Houston City Club, 12 May 1986; Cannady (photograph) on backpage, 147801 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Leading Edge 9, Aug. 1986; Cannady on pg. 8, 147800 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Report, Texas Society of Architects, Aug. 1986; Cannady on pg. 2, 147799 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Newsletter 9, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Sept. 1986; Cannady on pg. 6, 147798 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Houston Chamber of Commerce Magazine, Sept. 1986; Cannady on pg. 11, 147797 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Sun Living, Section of the Arizona Republic, 14 Sept. 1986; Cannady on pg. 2, 147796 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - College of Environmental Design News, Fall 1986; Cannady on pg. 25, 147795 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Newsletter 10, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, Nov. 1986; Cannady (Blake Summer House) on pg. 5, 147794 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Sallyport, publication of Rice Alumni, Nov. 1986-Jan. 1987; Cannady on pg. 22, 147793 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Center: A Journal for Architecture in America; Cannady (Blake House) on pgs 118-119, 1987; 149002 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Newsletter 1, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, January 1987; Cannady (Blake Summer House) on pg. 4, 147785 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Texas Architect, vol. 37 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1987; Cannady (Shulte Ranch) on pg. 35, 147784 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Invitation, "Art as Architecture," special evening of the Fort Bend Arts Council, 22 Jan. 1987, 147783 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Newsletter 2, Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, February 1987; Cannady (Windward Manor) on pg. 8, 147782 (Box 9, Folder 56)